<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Harley Inbody]]></title>
  <link href="http://harleyinbody.net/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harleyinbody.net/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-17T21:44:10-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://harleyinbody.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Harley Inbody]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rubygems Certificate Verify Failed]]></title>
    <link href="http://harleyinbody.net/blog/2014/02/11/rubygems-certificate-verify-failed/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-11T23:22:14-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://harleyinbody.net/blog/2014/02/11/rubygems-certificate-verify-failed</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When trying to bundle install on one of my Rails apps, I got an error saying
that &lsquo;certificate verify failed&rsquo;. I believe the rvm certificates were out of
date. What I found to work was <code>rvm rubygems latest</code>. After that I did my
<code>bin/bundle</code> and everything worked perfectly.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
    <link href="http://harleyinbody.net/blog/2014/01/02/welcome/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-02T13:49:28-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://harleyinbody.net/blog/2014/01/02/welcome</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my development blog. I am Harley and I will be your host. I am a
junior developer looking to make my way into the field full-time. I have an
A.A.S. in Computer Information Technology, and started to work on a B.S. in CS.
I am not currently attending school officially; but that doesn&rsquo;t mean that I&rsquo;m
not still studying and learning. I have worked with C++ and PHP in the past, but
am currently working with Ruby. I have one Rails project that I&rsquo;ve started
called <a href="http://bacon-splitter.herokuapp.com/" title="Bacon Splitter">Bacon Splitter</a>.
Feel free to check it out and provide feedback if you have any. I&rsquo;m also working
my way through the book &ldquo;Rails 4 in Action&rdquo; from
<a href="http://www.manning.com/bigg2/">Manning</a>, which has been a tremendous resource
for me. <!-- more --></p>

<p>I have wanted to start a dev blog for some time now, but the main impetus for me
starting this one now, comes from a few places. I&rsquo;ve been inspired by
<a href="https://twitter.com/Joshuakemp01">Joshua Kemp</a> and his story of going from no
degree to a junior developer in less than a year.
<a href="https://twitter.com/avdi">Avdi Grimm</a> has mentioned that he likes to read
developer blogs, so I hoped to give him one more source to read. Also,
<a href="https://twitter.com/marksim">Mark Sim</a>, one of my first remote pairing partners,
led me to Octopress as the framework to use. There are certainly other people
who have both inspired me, and helped me learn; and I hope to give them the
proper credit on this blog as we move forward.</p>

<p>I can be found on <a href="https://github.com/hinbody">Github</a> and
<a href="https://twitter.com/hinbody">Twitter</a>. Feel free to hit me up either place.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
